https://genotpicor.com/terms-of-use/

Skip to content
HomeBioRatesSchool ProgramsCommunity ProgramsFestival ProgramsEventsContact Me
HomeBioRatesSchool ProgramsCommunity ProgramsFestival ProgramsEventsContact Me
HomeBioRatesSchool ProgramsCommunity ProgramsFestival ProgramsEventsContact Me
Home » Terms of Use
Tools
To search for a word and highlight it on page use Ctrl + F To copy text from page, highlight text and then Ctrl + C To paste that text into another page, click page then Ctrl + V To search Internet, highlight text then right click Options List Current pixel font size is16
Click Tools to remove
Video IntroductionBioUpcoming Dates and EventsLa Compagnie at the Rogers City TheaterGenot Picor Storyteller VideoGenot Picor at West Hills Middle School, Bloomfield Hills Public SchoolsGrant Opportunities through the Michigan Arts and Humanities Council’s Touring DirectoryProject Based Learning (PBL) Activities for School PresentationsLa Compagnie VideoWebsite CreditsPrivacy PolicyTerms of Use
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. THEY GOVERN YOUR ACCESS AND USE OF THIS WEBSITE. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions concerning your use of this Website ("Terms of Use") and Storyteller Genot Picor’s Privacy Policy. Storyteller Genot Picormay make changes to the content of this Website, the Terms of Use, and Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. The revised Terms of Use and Privacy Policy shall be posted on this Website. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Website following any changes shall constitute your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, then you may not use this Website. Use of this WebsiteContents may be used solely for the furtherance of your relationship with Storyteller Genot Picor and you may not copy, use, modify, distribute, transfer, download, upload, resell, or republish any of the Contents of this Website without the prior written authorization of Storyteller Genot Picor. You must use this Website in compliance with all applicable laws. Copyrights and Other Intellectual PropertyExcept where otherwise expressly noted or as noted below, all materials and information contained on this Website, including but not limited to, all images, pictures, logos, illustrations, designs, photographs, video clips, text, icons, graphics, case studies, white papers, press releases, designs, overall appearance of this Website, and written and other materials that appear on this Website are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress or other intellectual property owned, controlled, or licensed (all of which, collectively, are herein referred to as the "Contents") by Storyteller Genot Picor or its affiliates or are the property of their respective owners that have been licensed to Storyteller Genot Picor and are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws and conventions. DisclaimerExcept where otherwise expressly noted or as noted below, all materials and information contained on this Website, including but not limited to, all images, pictures, logos, illustrations, designs, photographs, video clips, text, icons, graphics, case studies, white papers, press releases, designs, overall appearance of this Website, and written and other materials that appear on this Website are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress or other intellectual property owned, controlled, or licensed (all of which, collectively, are herein referred to as the "Contents") by Storyteller Genot Picor or its affiliates or are the property of their respective owners and are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws and conventions. Limitation of LiabilityIn no event shall “&a1&” be liable for any damages, including, without limitation, direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, punitive damages, or damages for loss of data, profits, revenue, incurred by you or any third party, whether under a contract, tort or any other theory of “&”liability, arising in connection with any party’s use of this Website or in connection with any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, line system failure, loss of data, or loss of use related to”&” this Website or any Website operated by any third party or any contents of this Website or any other Website, even if “&a1&” is aware of the possibility of such damages. IndemnityYou agree to defend, indemnity and hold harmless Storyteller Genot Picor, its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses or expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected with your access to or use of this Website or breach by you of the Terms of Use. SubmissionsIf you submit any information to Storyteller Genot Picor via this Website, the information shall be deemed and shall remain the property of Storyteller Genot Picor and Storyteller Genot Picor shall have the right to use that information in furtherance of Storyteller Genot Picors business. PasswordsYou are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password(s) you are given to access this Website and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password(s). You agree to notify Storyteller Genot Picor immediately of any unauthorized use of your password(s). Links to Third-Party Websites, Content, Products and ServicesStoryteller Genot Picor may establish links between this Website and one or more Websites operated by third parties. Storyteller Genot Picor has no control over any such other Websites, the contents therein or the products/services offered. The existence of any such links shall not constitute an endorsement, representation or warranty by Storyteller Genot Picor of such Websites, the contents of the third-party Websites, the products or services of such Websites or the operators of the Websites. Storyteller Genot Picor disclaims responsibility for the privacy policies and customer information practices of third-party Internet sites hyper linked to this Website. If you choose to purchase any products or services from a third party, your relationship is directly with the third party. You agree that Storyteller Genot Picor is not responsible for: (a) the quality of third-party products or services; and (b) fulfilling any of the terms of your agreement with the seller, including delivery of products or services and warranty obligations related to purchased products or services. You agree that Storyteller Genot Picor is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort you may incur from dealing with any third party. Termination of UseYou agree that Storyteller Genot Picor may, in its sole discretion, at any time terminate your access to this Website and any account(s) you may have in connection with this Website. Access to this Website may be monitored by Storyteller Genot Picor. Applicable LawAll matters relating to your access to, and use of, this Website shall be governed by U.S. federal law or the laws of the State of Michigan, without giving effect to its conflicts of laws principles. Any legal action or proceeding relating to your access to, or use of, this Website shall be instituted in a state or federal court in Warren, Michigan. You and Storyteller Genot Picor agree to submit to the jurisdiction of, and agree that venue is proper in, these courts in any such legal action or proceeding.
January 22, 2020 | AppWT
